Satyam Dubey

UI DEVELOPER

+91 8586864294 # SATYAMDUBEY9450@GMAIL.COM # NOIDA, INDIA

Summary

Skilled UI Developer with a strong background in developing applications for a diverse clientele. **6 +years** of hands-on experience includes programming, debugging and specifically engaged in, the development of World Wide Web applications. I deal with amazing technologies, tasks and people.

Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- GIT
- React JS
- SASS
- Media Query
- Emailer
- CMS
- Cross Browser Coding
- Pdf Convert

Experience

Company – Neosoft Technologies Pvt ltd (February 2024 – Present)
Profile – Sr. Front End
Developer,

Noida, India

Neosoft technologies pvt ltd is a premier IT services & solutions provider company providing cost effective IT servicesworldwide. It focused entirely around growing our client's businesses in a cost effective manner. The team of professionals has experience and specialized in providing high-demanding consulting and strategy planning requirements of our clients for software, web and mobile applications solutions.

- Developed websites using React.js with a focus on responsive design, ensuring optimal userexperience across various devices and screen sizes.
- Employed performance optimization techniques in Vue.js to achieve fast page loading times, improving overall website performance and user satisfaction.
- Implemented state management using React to efficiently manage the application state, ensuring seamless data flow and synchronization between components.
- Worked closely with cross-functional teams, including designers, backend developers, and QA
 engineers, to ensure cohesive project development and successful delivery.
- Designed and implemented custom React.js components to meet specific project requirements, promoting code reusability and maintainability.
- Successfully integrated APIs and services to enhance website functionality.

Company – Wenidi Technology Pvt. Ltd(April, 2023 – January 2024) Profile – Ui Developer Noida, India

Wenidi Technology is a premier IT services & solutions provider company providing cost effective IT servicesworldwide. It focused entirely around growing our client's businesses in a cost effective manner. The team of professionals has experience and specialized in providing high-demanding consulting and strategy planning requirements of our clients for software, web and mobile applications solutions.

- Developed websites using React.js with a focus on responsive design, ensuring optimal userexperience across various devices and screen sizes.
- Employed performance optimization techniques in Vue.js to achieve fast page loading times, improving overall website performance and user satisfaction.
- Implemented state management using React to efficiently manage the application state, ensuring seamless data flow and synchronization between components.
- Worked closely with cross-functional teams, including designers, backend developers, and QA
 engineers, to ensure cohesive project development and successful delivery.
- Designed and implemented custom React.js components to meet specific project requirements, promoting code reusability and maintainability.
- Successfully integrated APIs and services to enhance website functionality.

Company - RedDoorz (Feb, 2021 – April,2023) Profile – Ui Developer Noida, India

RedDoorz is Southeast Asia's largest and fastest growing, technology- driven hotel management & booking platform. With over 1000 properties across Southeast Asia, our vision is to enable people to travel more and provide an affordable, reliable stay in all major cities and destinations.

- Establish an interactive and dynamic website that guarantees high traffic, page views, and maximum user experience.
- Proactively liaised with the design team and project manager to ensure efficient and timely delivery of significant projects.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements.
- Design and Developed React.js related projects.

Company - GingerWebs Pvt ltd (Jan, 2017 - Jan, 2021) Profile – Ui Developer Noida, India

Ginger Webs is a leading technology company in assessment and testing industry. We are driven by an ideology to make unique, easy to use and futuristic applications. We are having a decade of experience in assessment industry.

- Developed front-end web pages with HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript.
- Designed responsive web pages and applications that met business and user goals increased user satisfaction.
- Designed and developed admit cards as per the client requirements.
- Diagnosed and troubleshoot different websites of the company's critical clients by deploying updated knowledge of the modern technologies and techniques in the industry.

Project Link

https://www.reddoorz.com/en-id/

https://www.redliving.id/

https://business.reddoorz.com/en/

https://grow.reddoorz.com/owners/sign in

https://onlinetestseriesmadeeasy.in/

https://damsdelhi.com/

https://www.thinkexam.com/

https://www.study24x7.com/

https://madeeasypublications.org/

http://nata.in/

http://www.kaushikismusicandus.com

http://www.wenidi.com

Education

Board of Technical Education (Diploma IT)

(Information Technology): 08/2014 - 09/2016, CSJM Collage Ambedkar Nagar (U.P)

Intermediate - 12th

(PCM): 07/2012 - 06/2013 Raj Inter Collage (U.P)

High School - 10th

(PCM): 07/2010 - 06/2011

Tulsi Purva Madhyamika Vidyalaya Azamgarh (U.P)

Engineering Skills & Achievements

- Hands on experience in Designed web Sites and mobile sites.
- Hands on experience on GIT.
- Completed my training on Html, css with Js in 2016. (at DICE academy)
- Made a personal project "Restaurant Management System" with the help of HTML, CSS, JS & Sql(for database).
- Hands on experience on design admit cards and pdf. (as per the client requirements)

Languages

- English
- Hindi

Interests

- Listening Songs
- Debate
- Standups
- Watching Movies

Personal Details

Name – Satyam Dubey

Contact No - +91 8586864294

PAN Card No - LAQPS2808R

Date of birth - 28/08/1995

Email ID - satyamdubey9450@gmail.com

Current Location - Noida, India

LinkedIn Profile - https://www.linkedin.com/in/satyam-dubey-730961166/

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the details mentioned above are in accordance with the truth and fact as per my knowledge and I hold the responsibility for correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Signature Satyam Dubey